A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Council on the Environment, 1970-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 32359], 1971-1979., Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 1-6)
  - Federal Environmental Impact Statements
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Chesapeake Bay Vessel Traffic Service, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Route 288, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Bicentennial Transportation Program, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19-20)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], National Cemetery, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 21-22)
    - VA [Veterans Administration], Replacement hospital in Richmond, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - DOD [Dept. of Defense], F-16 Beddown at Hill Air Force Base, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - DOA [Dept. of the Army], Fort Belvoir Military Reservation, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - DOA [Dept. of the Army], Fort Belvoir Family Housing Project, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
    - DOA [Dept. of the Army], Electronics Research and Development Command, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - DOA [Dept. of the Army], Disposal of Chemical Agent Identification Sets at Rocky Mountain Colorado, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - DOT [Dept. of Transportation], Fort Story military housing, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 30-31)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], Naval Oceanographic Center, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], POL Bulk pipelines, Norfolk Naval Supply Center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], Location of a fleet ballistic missle submarine support base, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], Air Installation Compatible Use Zone Easement, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], POL Bulk pipelines, Norfolk Naval Supply Center, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], Naval Oceanographic Center St. Louis, Mississippi, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - DON [Dept. of Navy], Fort Story Family Housing, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - DAC [Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce], Replace regional laboratory building at Harrisonburg, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 40-41)
    - ABC [Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control], New office building, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - VIBC, Jamestown Foundation, Tidewater Virginia Indian Pavillion, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 43-44)
    - COR [Commission of Outdoor Recreation] Appalachian Trail Right-of-Way, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - CED [Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development], False Cape State Park, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - CED [Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development], Lake Anna State Park, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - CED [Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development], Relocation of Division of Forestry, District No. 2, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - CED [Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development], York River State Park, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Bland Correctional Center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Chesterfield Intensive Treatment Learning Center #1, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Mecklenburg, Dinwiddie, Caroline, and Southampton Counties, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Green Springs, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Multi-purpose additions, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Mecklenburg Correctional Center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Powhatan Correctional Institute, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 57-58)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Southampton Mobile Homes, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], St. Brides Correctional Center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - DC [Dept. of Corrections], Yough Correctional Center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - VEC [Virginia Employment Commission], Norfolk local offices, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - DEB [Division of Engineering and Buildings], Proposed 14th Street Towers Office Complex, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - CGIF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Cap Charles Harbor Boat Ramp, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - CGIF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Crooked Creek Management Area, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - CGIF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Curtis Memorial County Park Fishing Lake, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - CGIF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Morley's Wharf Access Area, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - CGIF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Nottoway County Fishing Lake, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - CGIF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Pleasure House Creek public boat ramp, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Outlay projects, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Renovations to Richmond and Chesterfield offices, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], I-64, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - DIA [Dept. of Intergovernmental Affairs], Farmer's Home Administration, Vermicolite, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - VIMS [Virginia Institute of Marine Science], Sewage Treatment System for VIMS, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - DMHMR [Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Facility Bond Act, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - DMHMR [Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Catawba Hospital, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - DMHMR [Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation], Upgrade Water and Sewage Treatment Plants, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Series VII: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 32687], 1967-1982., Extent: 9.35 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 1-10)
  - ACOE [Army Corps of Engineers], 3 Year Environmental Impact Statements schedule, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - COE [Council on the Environment], Deauthorization List for Unconstructed Projects, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - FPR Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Marine Resource Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Southern Properties Development, New Kent County, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - FPR, Prior to establishment to procedures, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - FPR, Establishment of procedures, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Wetlands Commission, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Individual requests for permits, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - FDR, Norfolk district monthly permit discussions, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FPR, Colonial Pipeline Company, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Thompson-Arthur Paving Company, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - FPR, Transfer of responsibility to Council of Environment, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Blue Stone Lake, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Little Creek Water Supply Reservoir, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hampton Roads Water Supply, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - Prince William County Water Supply, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Plan for Philpott Lake, Wilmington District, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Kerr-Buggs Island Lake Protective Association, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Catoctin Dam, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Verona Dam, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Hipes Dam on Craig Creek, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Salem Church Dam, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 26-29)
  - Flannagan Dam and Reservoir, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Albemarle and Chesapeake Canal and Dismal Swamp canal, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Section 404 regulations, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Maintenance dredging of cranes, Greenvale and Queens Creek, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Quinby Creek, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Taskinas Creek Project, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Jarvis Creek, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Lynnhaven Inlet dredging, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Coastal Energy Impact Program, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Division of Legislative Services, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], Flood Plain Information, Kingsland Creek, Chesterfield County, Va., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], Flood Plain Information, Oldtown Creek, Chesterfield County, Va., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], James River Basin, Va., 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], Water filtration plant, Richmond, Va., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], Potomac River Water Supply Structure, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], Public Notice Concerning the Verona Lake, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - COE [Corps of Engineers], Peters Creek Basin, Roanoke County, Va., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Army Corps of Engineeers, Richmond Flood Control, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - EIS Workshop, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dept. of Corrections, Preplanning Justification and Study, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - DC & ED [Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development], Hungry Mother State Park, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CED [Dept. Conservation and Economic Development], Seashore State Park, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - CED [Dept. Conservation and Economic Development], Sky Meadows Park, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CED [Dept. Conservation and Economic Development], RoseAnn Coal Refuse Reclamation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CED [Dept. Conservation and Economic Development], Natural Resources Building, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ABC [Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control], Store No. 201, Abingdon, Va., 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ABC [Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control], Store No. 187, Richmond, Va., 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - DE & B [Division of Engineering and Buildings], Preplanning Justifications, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
  - Division of Legislative Services, General correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - JCP [Division of Justice and Crime Prevention], General correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Winchester loop, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], General correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Route I81, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Route I86, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Route I66, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Marshall Area and Arcola Area Maintenance Headquarters, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - DHT [Dept. of Highways and Transportation], Central Materials Laboratory, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - VHLC [Virginia Historic Landmarks Commission], Yorktown Cofferdam and Pier, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CG & IF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Long Creek Boat Ramp, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CG & IF [Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries], Capital Outlay Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - DE & B [Division of Engineering and Buildings], MCV-VCU Central Heating Plant, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Southside Electric Cooperative, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Charlottesville-Remington Transmission Line application (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Virginia Air Transportation Study, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Tangier Island Airport, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Dept. of Aviation, Tangier Island, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Shenandoah Valley, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Runway extension, Franklin, Va., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Patrick Henry Airport, Newport News, Va., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Dept. of Aviation, Norfolk Commercial Heliport permit application, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Norfolk International Airport, Master plan, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Regulations for the Control and Abatement of Air Pollution, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Aircraft storage hangar, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Airport permits, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - SCC [State Corporation Commission], Blue Ridge Airport, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Correspondence from, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Correspondence to, 1982 July-December (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Correspondence from, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Correspondence to, 1983 January-March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Correspondence to, 1983 April-June (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Correspondence to, 1983 July-September (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Responses written for Secretariat Betty J. Diener's signature, 1983 January-March (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Secretary Betty J. Diener, Comments on the condition of the Commonwealth, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Responses written for Secretariat Betty J. Diener's signature, 1983 April-June (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Responses written for Secretariat Betty J. Diener's signature, 1983 July-September (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Governor Robb, Drafts for signatures, 1982 January (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - (Box 4)
  - (Box 4)
  - Chronological files, 1976 September - October (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 1976 November - December (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1977 January (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1977 February (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files, 1977 March (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files, 1977 April (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files, 1977 May (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chronological files, 1977 June (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files, 1977 July (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files, 1977 August (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files, 1978 April (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Chronological files, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Chronological files, 1978 June (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chronological files, 1978 June-July (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chronological files, 1978 August (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Chronological files, 1978 September-October (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Chronological files, 1978 November-December (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chronological files, 1979 January-February (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Chronological files, 1973 March-August (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 1973 September-December (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1974 January-June (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1974 July-December (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files, 1975 January-April (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files, 1975 May-December (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files, 1976 June-August (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 33128], 1975-1988., Extent: cu. ft. ( boxes). (Box 1)
  - 
  - Correspondence from Richard L. Cook, 1985 Jan-Mar (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to Richard L. Cook, 1985 July-Aug (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to Richard L. Cook, 1985 Sept-Dec (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Information Technology meeting, 1985 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1983 Oct-Dec (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - EPA Journal article written by COE, 1985 Feb. 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Transitional Issue Paper Summary, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Marine Users Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from Dr. Betty J. Diener, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence from Dr. Betty J. Diener, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from Governor Charles S. Robb, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Responses written for Governor Robb's signature, 1984 Jan-Mar (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Responses written for Governor Robb's signature, 1984 Apr-June (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Responses written for Governor Robb's signature, 1984 July-Dec (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to Richard L. Cook, 1985 Jan-Mar (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to Richard L. Cook, 1985 Apr-June (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Responses written for Governor Robb's signature, 1983 Jan-June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Responses written for Governor Robb's signature, 1983 July-Dec (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaire on citizens' concerns and interests for Virginia's environment, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Status report, 1984 March (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Status reports, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7-11)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1979 Jan. 10 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1979 May 9 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1979 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1979 October 3 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1980 March 19 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1980 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1980 September 17 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1980 December 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1981 June 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1981 September 10 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1981 October 22 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1982 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Meeting, 1982 June 9 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Correspondence, 1976-1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Toxic Substances Advisory Council, Exemptions Sub-Committee Information, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Resources Information System Task Force, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 27-32)
  - (Box 4)
- Series IX: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 33747], 1977-1986., Extent: cu. ft. ( boxes). (Box 1)
  - 
- Series X: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 34993], 1985-1991., Extent: cu. ft. ( boxes). (Box 1)
  - 